lozo.com 2019-02-12

# Privacy Policy - LOZO

### Latest Update - March 4, 2016

This Privacy Policy was updated as of March 4, 2016. Your continued use of the LOZO website and/or the services offered by LOZO following any changes made to this privacy policy and/or terms of use will mean that you also accept the changes.

### General Disclaimers

**Except as set forth below or as specifically agreed to by you, LOZO LLC will not disclose any Personally Identifiable Information as gathered from you on our Sites.**

Except as otherwise noted, the content of our Website ([www.LOZO.com](http://www.lozo.com/)), including but not limited to text, graphics and icons, are copyrighted materials of **LOZO LLC** and its suppliers and affiliates, and contain trademarks, service marks and trade names of **LOZO LLC** and its suppliers and affiliates. ALL RIGHTS RESERVED. You may use the content ONLY for educational purposes only.

We make every effort to provide accurate and timely information; however, there may be inadvertent technical factual inaccuracies, omissions, and typographical errors, for which we apologize. Our Website and its content are delivered on an "as-is" and "as-available" basis. **LOZO LLC** cannot ensure that files you download from our Website will be free of viruses or contamination or destructive features. **LOZO LLC** reserves the right to make changes and corrections at any time, without notice.

Our online **Terms and Conditions/User Agreement** is considered the governing agreement between both you as a user of our Website and **LOZO LLC** , and it supercedes any other information on our Website. 

### Privacy Policy

**LOZO LLC** is committed to doing business with the highest ethical standards and appropriate internal controls. We are also committed to providing better service to our members. This Privacy Policy applies to all users of LOZO's Website published at www.LOZO.com (and any other websites with "LOZO" branding that link to this Privacy Policy, including, without limitation, desktop and mobile versions of the Website) and any mobile-device applications we offer now or in the future, such iOS and Android applications, that are branded "LOZO" and link or reference this Privacy Policy.

**LOZO LLC** adheres to the following policies with regards to your privacy.

## For All Users

### Definitions

"Non-Personal Information" is information that is in no way personally identifiable and that is obtained automatically through your use of our Website.

"Personally Identifiable Information" also "Personal Information" is non-public information that is personally identifiable and obtained in connection with providing a product or service to you. It may include information stored in your membership profile such as your name, email address, and other information you may provide.

"Website" is LOZO LLC's Website published at www.LOZO.com (and any other websites with "LOZO" branding that link to this Privacy Policy, including, without limitation, desktop and mobile versions of the Website) and any mobile-device applications we offer now or in the future, such iOS and Android applications, that are branded "LOZO" and link or reference this Privacy Policy.

### Personal Information Collected

Personal Information is information that can be used to identify or contact an individual, or to locate them. It also includes other non-personal information that may be associated with Personal Information. We may collect the following types of Personal Information:

  * Contact Information that allows us to communicate with you, such as your name, addresses, phone numbers, email addresses, social media website user account names, or other contacts at which you receive communications from or on behalf of LOZO LLC.
  * Interest-based Information that helps us to understand who you are and what types of products and advertisements you might like. This includes lifestyle information; geographic information such as your neighborhood; the types of coupons that interest you and don't interest you; information collected from social media interactions (such as via Facebook Connect); and demographic information (e.g., birth date, age, gender). We use Google Analytics to collect this data by using Google advertising cookies and anonymous identifiers. 
  * Shopping Preference Information about what categories, brands, and varieties of products you buy, such as the items you put on the shopping lists you share with LOZO, the search terms you enter into our Website, and the offers you select. This also includes the coupons you view and redeem, the third-party links you visit, and the stores you prefer.
  * Location Information that allows us to periodically determine your geolocation, such as your location relative to nearby stores or aisles.
  * Analytics Information about your use of our Services, such as your IP address, access time, device ID or other unique identifier (e.g., Android advertising ID), device name and model, operating system type, domain name, screen views, language information, and your activities on our Services. For example, information collection by our Services via a mobile device may include the following: (i) the names of the other applications on your mobile device and, if you use an Android-based mobile device, how you use them (e.g., frequency and duration of use); (ii) if you use an Android-based mobile device, the URL addresses of the webpages you access; (iii) information about your mobile device (e.g., make, model, operating system, and other similar information); (iv) information about your use of features, functions, or clicks on notifications or content; and (v) the unique identifier of a nearby Bluetooth® proximity beacon. 

### How LOZO LLC Collects Personal Information

We may ask you for Personal Information when you register, subscribe, create an account, or otherwise interact with the Website or contact LOZO LLC. For example, you may be required to provide us with Contact Information or Relationship Information in order to register for certain services.

We also collect Shopping Preference Information when you provide a grocery list upon registration, as you interact with offers on our Website, and if you contact us via telephone, email, text, mail, social media interaction, or other methods of communication, such as for customer support purposes.

If you use a social media platform, a mobile device or other third-party method of communication to interact with LOZO LLC or the Website, that platform may have a specific privacy statement that governs the use of Personal Information related to that platform. If you have questions about the security and privacy settings of your mobile device, please refer to instructions from your mobile service provider or the manufacturer of your device to learn how to adjust your settings.

If you use the Website on a mobile device and your mobile device's settings allow it, we may collect Personal Information from your mobile device. In addition, if you have also enabled Bluetooth® functionality on your mobile device, we may determine your presence and duration within a location, based on the detection of signals from nearby Bluetooth® proximity beacons. Our Services may be designed to collect information even if you are not logged into the Website.

From time to time, we may also supplement Personal Information with information collected from third parties, including demographic information, information about your interests, and similar information that the third parties have collected from other sources (which may include analytics data from third party websites). For example, we may collect information from third parties to enhance other information we have about you, to help us better understand you, and to otherwise enhance the Services.

### How LOZO LLC Uses Personal Information

LOZO LLC may use Personal Information to:

  * Operate and improve our services;
  * Provide users with advertisements for products and services from brands and stores, including coupons based on information such as your shopping list, the coupons you select, and anticipated interests, personal characteristics, and location;
  * Evaluate eligibility of users for certain coupons, products or services;
  * Evaluate the types of coupons, products or services that may be of interest to users;
  * Track redemption of coupons and perform other analytics;
  * Provide user support, including to our merchants or business partners;
  * Fulfill requests for LOZO LLC services;
  * Communicate and provide additional information that may be of interest to you about LOZO LLC and our merchants and business partners, such as LOZO LLC news, special offers and coupons, announcements, and marketing materials;
  * Send you reminders, technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages service bulletins, or marketing;
  * Provide advertisements to you through the Services, third-party sites, email messages, text messages, mobile-push notifications, or other methods of communication;
  * Administer surveys, sweepstakes, contests, or other promotional activities or events sponsored by us or our partners;
  * Create user profiles that may contain inferences about users such as age range, income range, gender, and interests;
  * Manage our everyday business needs such as website administration, analytics, fraud prevention, Terms of Use or to comply with the law;
  * Allow you to sign up for special offers from third parties through the Website; and 
  * Carry out other purposes that are disclosed to you and to which you consent.

### When and Why LOZO LLC Discloses Personal Information

We may share your Personal Information as required or permitted by law as described below:

  * With affiliated companies (e.g., subsidiaries and other companies owned by or controlled by LOZO LLC) who may only use the Personal Information for the purposes described in Section 3 above;
  * With our service providers that provide services for us to assist us in carrying out the purposes described above such as sending email and conducting surveys or sweepstakes on our behalf. Our service providers are bound by law or contract to protect Personal Information and are only allowed to use the Personal Information in accordance with the terms of our service agreements with them;
  * Brands and merchants, and the parent companies of those brands and merchants;
  * LOZO LLC business partners or advertisers, as part of an offer, contest, or other activity that is provided by or in conjunction with LOZO LLC and its business partners and in which you have elected to participate. For example, if you are referred to LOZO LLC from a business partner's website or through an invitation facilitated by or in conjunction with a LOZO LLC business partner, LOZO LLC may provide that business partner with Contact Information and Transactional Information to validate the referral and to support the terms of the relationship between LOZO LLC and the business partner, which may allow such business partner to contact you directly and to advertise to you; 
  * To effect a merger, acquisition, or otherwise; to support the sale or transfer of business assets; to enforce our rights or protect our property; to protect the rights, property or safety of others, investigate fraud, respond to a government request; or as needed to support auditing, compliance, and corporate governance functions. We may also disclose Personal Information to defend ourselves in litigation or a regulatory action, and when required or advised to do so by law, such as in response to a subpoena, or similar legal process, including to law enforcement agencies, regulators, and courts in the United States and other countries where we operate. If LOZO LLC is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on one or more of our Services of any change in ownership or uses of your Personal Information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your Personal Information; or 
  * Otherwise with your consent. We encourage LOZO LLC merchants and business partners to adopt and post privacy policies. However, the use of your Personal Information by such parties is governed by the privacy policies of such parties and is not subject to our control. When you choose to interact with a LOZO LLC merchant or business partner, we encourage you to read any privacy policy they may have posted on their website.

We may also disclose information about you that is not personally identifiable. For example, we may provide our merchants, business partners, or other third parties with reports that contain aggregated and statistical data about our users.

### Cookies and Related Technologies

When you use our Website, we collect certain information by automated or electronic means, using technologies such as cookies, flash local storage objects, pixel tags, web beacons (also called '1x1 pixel,' 'pixel,' 'Floodlight tag,' 'Spotlight tag,'), browser analysis tools, and web server logs. As you use our Website, your browser and devices communicate with servers operated by us, our business partners and services providers to coordinate and record the interactivity and fill your requests for services and information. We may also use this to track transaction information, such as the printing or redemption of a coupon, with third-party affiliate network operators. Additional information on how to opt-out of certain tracking features is set forth in the Your Choices section below. 

The information from cookies and related technology is stored in web server logs and also in web cookies kept on your computers or mobile devices, which are then transmitted back to our Website by your computers or mobile devices. These servers are operated and the cookies managed by us, our business partners or our service providers.

Some cookies are temporary, whereas others may be configured to last longer. "Session" cookies are temporary cookies used for various reasons, such as to manage page views. Your browser usually erases Session cookies once you exit your browser. "Persistent" cookies are more permanent cookies that are stored on your computers or mobile devices even beyond when you exit your browser. We may use Persistent cookies for a number of purposes, such as retrieving certain information you have previously provided (such as your user id if you asked to be remembered), and storing your preferences.

We collect many different types of information from cookies and other technologies. For example, we may collect information from the devices you use to access our Services, your operating system type or mobile device model, browser type, domain, and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone of your device. Browsers routinely send these types of information to web servers. Our server logs also record the Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses of the devices you use to interact with the Services. An IP address is a unique identifier that devices use to identify and communicate with each other on the Internet. We may also collect information about the website you were visiting before you came to our Services and the website you visit after you leave our Services, if this information is supplied to us by your browser.

We use third-party advertising and data service companies to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Our third-party partners may use code, web beacons, cookies, clear gifs and other technologies on our pages that allows them to access cookies on our websites and widgets, and to help such parties track their marketing campaigns and the general usage patterns of visitors to their websites. This Privacy Policy does not cover the collection methods or use of the information collected by these third parties, and LOZO LLC is not responsible for cookies or clear gifs in third party ads. We encourage you to review the privacy policies or statements of these third party advertising companies to learn more about their use of cookies and other technologies.

For emails, we work with data providers such as LiveIntent, who may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser to enable you to receive customized ads, content or services. No personally identifiable information is placed into these cookies. The cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you voluntarily have submitted to us, e.g., your email address, in hashed, non-human readable form. Additionally, emails we send may contain a bit of code known as a "web beacon." This code allows us to understand the time and date of when a user has opened an email and when he/she has utilized a link within the email to visit a website. Our web beacons do not collect personally identifiable information. Users wishing to disable our web beacons should do so by turning images "off" in their email client (e.g., Outlook, Outlook Express). Please see your email client for more information.

We have relationships with third party advertising technology and analytics companies, such as Google Analytics and IgnitionOne, to place advertisements on our behalf onto other websites, and to perform tracking and reporting functions for our Services and our advertisements. These third parties may automatically collect information about your visit to our Services and other websites, your IP address, web log data, information about your operating system, your ISP and the browser you use to visit our Services. We may share with these third parties certain de-identified demographic or other data linked to data you have provided us, as well as your email address in hashed (non-readable) form.

We use a third-party service provider to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on this site. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web site, and your interaction with our products and services, including details about the coupons you select. They may also use information about your visits to this and other Web sites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp. You can opt out of having your anonymous information collected by our customizing service by visiting the link above or <http://optout.netmng.com/optout.php>. If you select the “opt out” button there, we will delete your existing netmining.com cookie(s) and try to place a new cookie that instructs us not to track your future activities when we detect that cookie. If your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit our opt-out page, we cannot set our no-track cookie. Also, if you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different computer or change web browsers, you will need to opt-out again.

We allow Magnetic to monitor Company affiliated sites for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisements, “click-throughs” and/or other activities, and Magnetic may use cookies, web beacons and other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our users. For further information about Magnetic's search re-targeting product, Magnetic’s homepage is located at http://www.magnetic.com. The full text of Magnetic’s privacy policy is available on the Web at http://privacy.magnetic.com. Magnetic may allow third parties to monitor Magnetic associated sites for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisements, “click-throughs” and/or other activities, and such third parties may use cookies, web beacons and other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about Magnetic users. Users may go to http://magnetic.com for information on what is being tracked. Users may go to http://privacy.magnetic.com/w3c/optout.html for information on how to opt-in or opt-out of use of their information by Magnetic and may go to http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp to opt-out of most third party tracking. 

### Your Choices

We think that you benefit from a more personalized experience when we know more about you and the kinds of coupons you like. However, you can limit the information you provide to LOZO LLC, and you can limit the communications that LOZO LLC sends to you.

### Email

You can manage your email preferences by logging into My Account on LOZO.com and visiting the My List Preferences tab. You can also manage your subscriptions by following subscription management instructions contained in the commercial messages that we send you. You may choose to subscribe to some types of messages, and may choose to unsubscribe from others. You may also update your subscription preferences from time to time. If you wish to opt out of receiving offers directly from LOZO LLC merchants or business partners, you can follow the opt-out instructions in the emails that they send you.

To opt-out of email cookies or learn more please go to http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. To disable email web beacons, turn images "off" in your email client (e.g., Outlook, Outlook Express). Please see your email client for more information.

### Opting Out of Tracking

You may manage how your browser handles cookies and related technologies by adjusting its privacy and security settings. Browsers are different, so refer to instructions related to your browser to learn about cookie-related and other privacy and security settings that may be available. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your computer from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. You can opt-out of being targeted by certain third party advertising companies online at http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/. In addition, you can opt out of Google Analytics cookies at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/.

### Use of Aggregate Data

LOZO LLC may combine Non-Personal Information you provide through our Website with information from other users to create aggregate data that may be disclosed to third parties. Aggregate Information does not contain any information that could be used to contact or identify you. For example, we may use information gathered to create a composite profile of all the users of a particular third party site. These third party websites may use this information to design appropriate programs and activities on their site. Depending on the circumstances, we may or may not charge third parties for this Aggregate Information. In any case, LOZO LLC will not disclose your Personally-Identifiable Information to any third party without your prior permission, except as otherwise permitted by this Privacy Policy. We require parties with whom we share Aggregate Information to agree that they will not attempt by any means or use of other parties to transform such information into Personally Identifiable Information.

### Exemptions from Privacy Policy

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you may send to the **LOZO LLC** by email or instant messaging programs (i.e. AOL, Yahoo, etc.), as email and instant messages are not recognized as a secure communication forms. As such, we request that you do not send any information, which you consider private, to us by email or instant message. Likewise, our Website has Wikis, message boards, and other posting areas that are open to the general public. Anything posted on such Wikis, message boards, or other posting areas will not be private in any fashion. As such, take special care in posting information, especially when you consider such information to be of a private nature.

### Use of Credit Cards

LOZO does not currently charge for its services, and does not collect any payment information. If we choose to offer paid services in the future, to purchase those services from our Website, you may have to provide a credit card for billing purposes. We will use 3rd party billing services and HAVE NO CONTROL over these services. We will use our best efforts to make sure that your credit card number is kept STRICTLY CONFIDENTIAL by using only 3rd party billing services that use the latest security encryption technology to protect your credit card number from unauthorized use. However, you understand and agree that we are in no way responsible for any misuse of your credit card number.

### Use By Minors

**LOZO LLC** is committed to protecting the privacy of children. There may be good and/or services offered by members of our Website that are not designed nor intended for use by individuals under a specific age. **LOZO LLC** is not responsible for determining the age of its users and has no liability whatsoever should a minor use our Website to acquire goods and/or services that would otherwise be prohibited due to the minor's age. **LOZO LLC** encourages parents to monitor their children's Internet usage as a result.

### Links to Other Websites

Our Website contains links to other websites. **LOZO LLC** is not responsible for the actions, practices, or content of such websites linked to or from our Website.

### CAN-SPAM Compliance Notice

**LOZO LLC** and its affiliates fully comply with the federal CAN-SPAM Act. You can always opt out of receipt of further email correspondence from us. 

### Transfer of Ownership

If the entire or substantial ownership of our Website were to change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, your user information would remain subject to the promises of our then current Privacy Policy. 

### Your Acceptance of This Privacy Policy

This is our entire Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. You agree to it every time you use our Website. 

### Questions About This Privacy Policy

Should you have a privacy question about our Website, please email our customer service department ([admin@LOZO.com](mailto:admin@lozo.com)).

## Additional Privacy Policy Items For Members

### General

As a Member, when you register with our Website, you provide us with certain Personally Identifiable Information, such as your name, your email address, your address, and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us. We may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. Members post Content, as defined in our online User Agreement, on our Website at their own risk. We are not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on our Website. You understand and agree that even after their removal, copies of your Content may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or in copies made by other users of our Website. Any improper collection or misuse of information on our Website is a violation of our Terms & Conditions/User Agreement and should be reported to [admin@LOZO.com](mailto:admin@lozo.com). 

### Security Policy & User ID/Password

Our site utilizes various information security measures such as internet firewalls, an intrusion detection system, encrypted data transmission, and operating procedures to protect your personal data, accounts, passwords, etc. This information is kept completely separate and confidential; there is no chance of any other user seeing your information unless you have given them your user ID and password. As such, you should protect your user ID and password and NOT share it with anyone. **If you believe your user ID and password have been compromised, please contact our technical support department so they can issue you a new user ID/password (**[admin@LOZO.com](mailto:admin@lozo.com) **)**.

### Registration Information

You will provide us information about yourself when you register to be a member of **LOZO LLC** , register for certain services, or register for email newsletters and alerts. You may also provide additional comments on how you see **LOZO LLC** servicing your needs and interests. 

### Use of Member Information

When you register as a Member with **LOZO LLC** , you create your own member profile. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by **LOZO LLC** that we think you may find valuable. Profile information is used by **LOZO LLC** primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access our Website.

We may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. For instance, a contact sends you a new message or responds to your post on a forum thread, you may receive an email alerting you to that fact. 

If you register as a Member, we require you to submit Personally Identifiable Information. You are responsible for ensuring the accuracy of the Personally Identifiable Information you submit to **LOZO LLC**. Inaccurate information will affect the information you receive when using our site and tools and our ability to contact you as described in this Privacy Policy (i.e. your email address should be kept current). 

### Message Boards, Wikis, and Other Public Forums

**LOZO LLC** also offers message boards, Wikis, and other public forums where only Members can post. All information posted to these public forums is open to the general public. Do not post any content or communication here that you wish to remain private.
